Muzamil Sabir

Full Stack Web Developer

contact



bozdarmuzamil8egmail.com

Kumbhar Paraa Sindh,Pakistan

www.MuzamilSabir.com

Skills

Language

- English
- Simdhi
- Urdu



About US

As a passionate and versatile Full Stack devoloper, I am successful at turning concepts into visually appealing development. With over 1 Years of comprehensive experience in Full Stack Web Development. Accompained by a bachlor degree degree in Information Technology (IT)

Work Experience

Web Development | Institute of of Computer Center Tando Allahyar | Feb 2021 - 2023

• Collaborated with clients to understand their devolop needs.

Freelance Full Stack Web Developer | Self-Employed | June 2024 - Present

 Collaborated directly with clients to assess develop needs, goals, and target audiences.

Education

- Higher Secondry School School (HSC) in Institute Institute of MHSS Tando Allahyar Sindh, Pakistan (2021–2022) Grade A
- Bacholor of Information Technology (IT) in SAU Tandojam Sindh Pakistan 2022 Batch Continue....